If you're not leaving back your other items on ten.
Hey!
Any second now, I think we're looking for a Brad Pitt look alike.
If we're set up a 415, they will the Godhead ages all ten terms.
We'll get the team over here now.
Get out of my car!
Oh, man!
Please, come inside!
Please!
Anyone in the floor?
No!
Oh, man!
He can't!
Not you, sweetie.
Hey, Brad.
Carefully take out your weapon holding the butt with two fingers only.
Slowly place it on the floor and take three steps back.
What is this?
I don't know.
Weird.
Mr. Bean, are you present on any kind of medication?
Not the die-dough.
Well, you can certainly use some.
So, doctor?
Uh...
Yes, okay, doctor Bean.
Well, you made it.
Nice flight.
Woo!
Well, this is Kevin.
Oh.
And this is Jennifer.
She's been very excited about meeting you.
Uh-huh.
My wife, Allison.
Woo!
David?
Could I just have the tennis talk with you in the kitchen?
All right, yeah.
Let's go.
I appreciate that on first viewing he seems a little eccentric.
David, there are Martians who have been exiled from Mars for looking weird
who look less weird than this guy.
He is an original quality.
He goes today.
Wow, that was amazing.
It's really cool.
Hey, can you do this?
No, but I can do this.
Steve!
How do you do that?
Magic.
I'm doing it.
So, you're going to tell him today?
Yes, today, today, today.
Today seems like a good day.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, okay.
Well, sir.
And on the orthodox start.
I guess I never expected things with a man of your caliber to be normal.
I got a confess.
I've never actually read anything you've written.
Tell me, doctor, what exactly is your position at the gallery?
I sit in the corner.
I look at the paintings.
Ah!
That is brilliant.
If only more scholars would do that, you know, just sit and look.
You know, not lecture and write and argue.
Just sit and look at the paintings themselves.
Now, that is brilliant.
Yep.
Yes.
Morning, Albert.
Good morning, sir.
Dr. B?
Oh.
You'd like to sign in, sir?
Thank you.
Welcome to the Crescent, Dr. B.
Welcome to my world.
You were expected in Pearson's office at 9 a.m.
Now, this is a man who does not like to be kept waiting.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Absolutely.
You bet.
All right.
Hmm.
Oh, man.
Oh, oh.
Oh.
Dr. B, we should make a move. We're very light.
Hmm.
Oh.
Oh, we...
Dr. B, if you...
When you're ready.
Oh, okay.
Uh, David, finally.
And this must be our professor from across the sea.
Yes, George Grocer.
This is Dr. B.
I'm delighted, Dr. B.
I'm not going to be on the field.
Please, sir.
You're doing a great deal about your doctor.
Thank you, Dr. B.
It's a great deal, love you.
And this is Bernice, a charge of PR.
An absolute honor, Dr. B.
I'm not going to be on the field.
Please, sir.
An absolute honor, Dr. B.
All right, thank you.
And Walter Huntley, our merchandise manager.
Hmm.
Nice to meet you.
Moving along, take a seat, Dr. B.
You...
Sir, let me take that old thing.
This is very out of date.
Thank you.
Before we settle it, we might want to feast your eyes on these.
Well, I'll be honest with you, Bernice.
I like this.
It's beautiful, sir.
Hmm.
Thank you.
It is.
Yeah.
Over here.
Okay.
Hmm.
Lovely green.