Subscribe to Shemaru Comedy and press the bell icon.
This is the train.
Open the train and take the ticket and the road roller.
And red belt.
All four of them are complete.
Now you can take the road roller.
You are not worried about people.
But tell your officer.
Don't play with the ticket.
What happened?
How did this road roller come to my office?
Come.
If you try to do anything,
I will take all the buildings.
And write down the details of the company's municipal office.
Please.
This is the government's office.
Don't play with the show.
I was just telling my sister.
She will go to her house.
Now roll the roller.
The hotel is in the police station.
Your youth will be arrested.
The risk is Rs. 500.
The rest is Rs. 300.
Your father's, your father's, brother's, brother's, brother's.
Come on.
Work hard.
Go to sleep.
Get out of here.
Get out.
This is Rs. 8,900.
The tea is different.
I was telling you to break the glass.
I didn't tell you to break the glass.
What do you do in the middle?
I break it.
Hey, boss.
I am going to die.
You are so stupid.
You are going to die.
Hey, you!
I am going to die.
You go.
Where are you going?
I will send the money.
Go.
Come on.
I have to see the captain.
I am going to see the captain.
He is the captain.
Come on.
When are you going to see?
Look.
Yes, the captain is the captain.
Yes.
Madam.
This is your road roller.
You should be ashamed.
No Indian who is crazy
will not do anything with his country.
Madam, where is Indim?
I will go to America.
I will go to Germany.
I will go to France.
I will go to England.
I will go to India.
I will go to America.
I will go to Punjabi, Malayali, Bangali.
Where is Indim?
This country will only be in one place.
You will see the country.
It is India and Pakistan's cricket match.
You will not get any country.
You will get all your worries.
That's all.
Good bye, madam.
And yes.
Madam, when I started to drive the car to the municipality..
..you had to take your car.
Your car has gone and your name has gone bad.
I apologize to you.
Okay, madam?
Okay.
Bye.
You got a cool car.
It's a car.
You can drive it.
It's a car license.
You need a driver or a license.
Do you know anyone?
Yes.
I know a driver.
You can take your car.
I will take it.
Go ahead.
Yes.
I asked the first question.
I said, no one will be here.
If you ask me, I will ask you.
I will ask you.
Yes.
I have no question.
You will hear.
No, no.
I will drive.
Don't be afraid.
sheets.
Inside it is a big port.
Yes.
You are counting me.
How is Gunlwice going to engage with one another characters?
Spread the shady gossip theory around hspecy dark wild now.
People are watching around.
Do you see each other?
Are you talking?
I heard.
With love of K interpret making salt cake hahah.
No.
Why?
I told you all these time.
These are the three other days
Then the deadly ram.
They'll bolt into the rock.
Next, the RC land.
This is a real house!
What happened?
You must have been raised from the roller.
You were talking about the roller.
The public was shouting and the roller was going to the wall.
The wall was going to the wall.
The roller was going to the wall.
The wall!
This is the wall.
The public was looking.
I was surprised.
I came up with a avo.
I came up with a filter.
I came up with a filter after a long time.
I was amazed to know you and my shoes were all weighted.
You and my shoes?
Yes, I speak about your face and mprobably.
I didn't do anything else?
Oh no.
No!
No, no, no.
Hey, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go.
Hey, wait a minute.
Hey, wait.
We're all safe.
You go, you go.
Hey, go, go.
He'll show you the right way.
Get out of here.
Cheety.
Looks like you're dead, sir.
What do you want?
Cheety.
What are you saying, sir?
You're mad, man.
Hey, boss.
Give me the tea.
Take this.
Give it to the owner.
You're going to get a meal and buy it.
Yes, I know.
I'm going to get a meal and buy it for Rs. 400,000.
Rs. 500,000, Rs. 500,000.
And you're going to get a meal from India.
You're not going to get a meal?
Yes, brother.
I have to give it to anyone.
I have to give it to everyone.
I've written down this story.
And if I start walking on this road once again,
I'll give you a pipe.
I'll save your money.
Okay.
Hey, you!
You'll give me a pipe.
Okay.
Hey, you!
Get it.
I've put it on the bed.
Then I'll give you a pipe.
Hey, you!
Yes.
Give it to everyone.
Come on.
Here.
You'll give me a pipe.
Yes.
What's the problem?
Nothing can be seen from here.
Hey, you!
You'll get a pipe.
Get it.
Hey, you!
You're going to die here.
Tell me.
Hey, you!
Get it.
You can't come here with me.
We'll go.
I'll go now.
Come on.
You're tied.
What happened?
Come on.
Whenever you tie a pipe, why do you tie it?
Where do you tie it?
This is when you tie a pipe.
This is tied.
Where do you tie it?
Hmm.
I'll check the pipe.
Who helps you?
I have a problem with the pipe.
I have a spark plug.
Hey, Lonkard!
Yes.
Open the pipe and give me the pipe.
Here.
Get it.
You're tied.
Come on.
Hey, you're tied.
You're tied.
You were tied.
Who was it?
What happened now?
I broke the gate box and I'll fix it now.
I'll fix it.
I'll fix it now.
What do I do now?
Do you hear the car, I'll hear it.
I'll hear it in a story.
I'll kill you.
Kill him.
Now you understand what's going on.
This is the entire Garbaghwar.
Garbagh.
But you'll get a lot of work.
You can go and get the last one.
You'll get a lot of work.
Stop it.
What do you want to do?
Tell me what you want to do.
Stop it.
You can't get a single bullet.
You'll get a gun.
Oh, yes.
Tell me what you want.
Do you want anything else?
Two or three of them.
I think the first one is very good.
But if we get a lot of work, we'll know what's going on.
We'll know what's going on.
I think we'll get a bullet from the bullet.
That's good.
Hey, Lottaker.
Hey,书 guy, why would you take over my sails and go.
What is that?
So clean it.
Oh, brother.
Just a minute.
Hey, let me clean it.
What do you want?
Nothing. It's 4 o'clock in the morning.
How long will you finish work?
You're right. I'm not in the right place.
Hey!
I'll just listen to this line.
I'll just come in.
Come on, do one thing.
My money is in the water.
I'll take you to the station.
You're not leaving from here?
What did you say?
I said, you're not leaving from here till now.
If I left from here, then I'd have been here.
This is your property.
Yes.
And now we're on our property.
If we don't take this time from here, then I'll have to pay you for every hour.
Stop talking.
No, madam. I'll take you from here.
If we don't take this time, then we'll pay you Rs. 10,000.
Why? Why?
We'll pay you Rs. 10,000.
Your problem will be solved.
If we don't take this time, then we'll do it on road.
We're done. Show us.
Yes, I'll show you.
Show us.
Are you scared?
And if we can't take this time, then we'll pay you for this.
And we'll pay you for this.
We'll get the money from you.
You've seen your money from the last hour.
You've told me to fix it.
I'll fix it.
I can't give you this guarantee.
If you don't trust me, then give us Rs. 5,400,000.
And leave us.
Rs. 5,400,000?
What's the matter?
To make her mad?
To keep her open to everyone.
Tell me.
Who told you to open it?
Listen. This is my mistake.
No, no.
Look, don't make a mistake here.
What?
Is this a headache?
You two are headache.
You don't need anything.
What happened?
How can you take this out of here?
Take this bagel out of the house.
Who said that?
I said that.
No, no.
One minute.
What is this?
Take this bagel out of here.
Brother, let us take this out of hand.
No, no.
Listen.
There is no other way out of this.
I will go and take this.
Don't make a mistake.
Yes, brother.
Yes.
I will go to the house.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Nothing, brother, no.
No, no.
Okay.
What is this?
No, no!
No, no.
No, no, no.
f
U
for
you
Her Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Guard!
He shoots!
I'm in for a gun!
Guard, guard!
Guard, guard, guard!
He's in front of me!
Take him away!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Get out of here!
Get out!
Stop!
Get out of here!
Get out!
What the hell is going on here?
Get out of here!
Get out!
What are you doing?
Ah liftoche
There she runs
Who has gone?
It's pacissou
What the heck?
Someone on the left
I patients direct
Get it
Ayyeo
Ah
If we go again
I will confide that
Ayyeo
Please
Should we just go for